* **Features**

### 15% OFF

GlassWire’s Personal Plan \*

Answer [3 quick questions](https://www.glasswire.com/intro-survey/) and claim your discount!

[Go to the Survey](https://www.glasswire.com/intro-survey/) \* Valid for new purchases only

Glasswire Website Privacy Policy
================================

Last Updated: April 12, 2024

Glasswire is committed to respecting your privacy. This Website Privacy Policy explains the ways in which Glasswire, a brand owned by Domotz Inc, and its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, ”Domotz”, “Glasswire”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) collect, use, and disclose information about you through our websites including Glasswire.com and Glasswire.com sub-domains (the “Site”).

This Website Privacy Policy was last updated in October 2021. We may change it from time to time, so please check back regularly to keep informed of any updates.

### Data collection

You may create an account with Glasswire to receive marketing communications, join our forum or post on our blogs.

_Information You Provide:_ We collect, and associate with your account, any information that you provide Glasswire when you use the Site, such as when you create an account, purchase a product, or contact us. Information you provide us can include, but is not limited to, (a) your name, email address, physical address, username, password, and other registration information; (b) transaction-related information, such as billing and shipping addresses, and any other information necessary to complete the transaction; (c) and information you provide when you contact us.

We do not collect or store your credit card information. Our credit card processing service provider will collect and store full payment card information from you.

_Usage:_ We collect information from and about the devices you use to access the Site. This includes things like IP addresses, the type of browser and device you use, the web page you visited before coming to the Site, and identifiers associated with your devices.

_Cookies and other technologies:_ We use cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies (“Cookies”) to provide, improve, protect and promote our services, as explained in the Cookies Policy section below.

_Third Party Sites and Social Media Features:_ Our Site contains links to other websites operated by third parties, such as social media companies Youtube and Twitter. These third party sites may collect information about you if you click on a link and they may record information about your browsing behaviour. Your interaction with these features is governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them. We do not control what information these third parties collect. Please review their privacy policies and your privacy settings on your social media sites and think carefully before clicking on third party links.

We do not currently respond to web browser “do not track” signals or other mechanisms that provide a method to opt out of the collection of information across the networks of websites and online services in which we participate. If we do so in the future, we will describe how we do so in this Website Privacy Policy. Visit [allaboutdnt.org](https://allaboutdnt.com/) for more information.

### Data Use

We may use the information we collect to provide, improve and protect our services, such as for:

* Delivering marketing communications about Glasswire-related services, products or promotions. We may use service providers to send these messages on our behalf, but we do not share your email address with any other third parties without your permission.
* Providing you with products, services, or information you request, for example when you contact us for remote support and troubleshooting;
* Providing you with information about the Site or required notices;
* Customizing your experience when using the Site;
* Improving the Site and services that we provide, such as by better tailoring our content to your needs and preferences;
* Generating and analyzing statistics about your use of the Site;
* Detecting, preventing, and responding to fraud, intellectual property infringement, violations of law, or other misuse of the Site.

We may also combine or aggregate any of the information collected through the Site or elsewhere for any of these purposes.

### Data Sharing

We do not share personal information for any commercial or marketing purpose unrelated to the delivery of Glasswire products and services without asking you first. We do not rent or sell our customer lists.

The following are the limited situations where we may share personal information:

_Trusted Partners working for Glasswire:_ Glasswire may occasionally use certain third party service providers to help us provide, improve, protect, and promote our services. These third parties may access your information only to perform tasks on our behalf and in compliance with this Website Privacy Policy.

_Other users:_ Certain features on the Site may allow you to share information with other users, such as your name, email address and additional information. Please take care if you choose to do so, as we do not control how these other users will handle your information.

_Business Transitions:_ If we are involved in a merger, acquisition or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information may be transferred as part of that deal. We will use reasonable efforts to try to ensure that the purchaser uses your personal information in a manner that is consistent with this Website Privacy Policy.

_Law & Order:_ We may disclose your information to third parties if we determine that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with the law; (b) protect any person from death or serious bodily injury; (c) prevent fraud or abuse of Glasswire or our users; or (d) protect Glasswire’s property rights.

We may share some aggregated, anonymized and non-personal information publicly and with our partners. For example, we may publish trends about internet speed, or statistics about the type of electronic devices installed in the homes of our customers. This information may also be shared with other users to help them understand their network as compared to others in the Glasswire community, raise awareness about technical issues or help us generally improve our system. We take steps to ensure this non-personal information is not being associated with any specific user and we require our partners to do the same.

### Cookie Policy

We use cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies (referred to collectively throughout this policy as “Cookies”) to provide, improve, protect and promote our services. Cookies help us with things like remembering your username for your next visit, and allow us to collect information about your browsing behaviour when you use our Site, including for example, browser type, IP address, domains, page views, referring/exit pages, and information about how you interact with our web pages. In some of our email messages, we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Site. We may track this click-through data to help us measure the effectiveness of our customer communications.

Our site uses first party cookies (i.e. cookies set directly by us to your device) as well as cookies served by third parties for the purposes outlined below. Some of the Cookies the Site uses only remain on your device while your browser is open (these cookies are known as “session cookies”) while others remain for longer periods (these are known as “permanent cookies”). The Site uses the following Cookies:

* Google Ads Cookies
* Google Tag Manager Cookies
* Google Analytics Cookies
* Google Display and remarketing Cookies
* Facebook Advertising cookies

You have the right to choose whether or not to accept Cookies. However, they are an important part of how our Site works, so you should be aware that if you choose to refuse or remove cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of the site.

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. To do so, please follow the instructions provided by your browser which are usually located within the “Help,” “Tools” or “Edit” facility. Some third parties also provide the ability to refuse their cookies directly by clicking on an opt-out link, and we have indicated where this is possible in the table above.

Further information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your device and how to manage and delete them, is available at the following URLs: [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.youronlinechoices.eu](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

### Data security & retention

_Security:_ We take security seriously and care about the integrity of your personal information. We use administrative, physical, and technical safeguards to protect the confidentiality of personally identifiable information, including encryption, firewalls and SSL (Secure Sockets Layer).

_Retention:_ We will retain your information for as long as your account is active, as needed to provide you services or as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or to enforce our agreements.

_Where:_ To provide you with our services, we may store, process and transmit information in locations around the world – including those outside your country. Those countries may not provide the same level of protection for your personal information as your home country, and may be available to the governments or agencies under a lawful order of those countries. Where this is the case, we will use reasonable efforts to try to ensure that your personal information is protected in accordance with this Website Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you consent to such transfer to, and processing in, these countries. Information may also be stored locally on the devices you use to access the services.

### Children

This Site is not directed to, nor do we knowingly collect information from, children under the age of 16. If you become aware that a child under your care has provided us with information without your consent, please contact us at the contact information below.

### Your Choice

If you no longer wish to receive non-transactional communications from us, please click the “unsubscribe” link in any email from us, update your marketing preferences in your account, or contact us at the address below.

To make a request to have personal information maintained by us returned to you, amended or removed, please email **privacy@glasswire.com**. Requests to access, change, or remove your information will be handled within thirty (30) days.

### Updates to this Policy

We may revise this Website Privacy Policy, from time to time, and will post the most current version on our website. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to this Website Privacy Policy. If a revision materially changes your rights, we will notify you and provide you with the opportunity to consent to such changes before applying them to that information.

### Contact

If your contact information changes, if you no longer wish to receive marketing communications from us, if you wish to inquire about information we have collected about you, or if you have questions or concerns about Glasswire privacy, please contact us at **privacy@glasswire.com**.

GlassWire

Resources

Keep in touch

Support

Legal

Cybersecurity News

Learn new ways to protect your computer and phone from online threats.

© 2024 GlassWire 

Try GlassWire Firewall for Android

GlassWire

Keep in touch

Support

Legal

Cybersecurity News

Learn new ways to protect your computer and phone from online threats.
